studysite.org 2019-06-29

# StudySite.org - Privacy Policy

_About Privacy [Terms and Conditions]_

_Privacy Statement for StudySite.org_

The following statements describes the privacy practices for StudySite.org

  * As a visitor to StudySite.org, your privacy is important to us.
  * We never sell any personal information collected from this websit
  * We do not collect any personal information from our users
  * Visits are logged for aggregate statistics and diagnosis
  * Security settings protect the misuse of sensitive information

_Log IN Information_

This is an OPTIONAL service provided by StudySite.org Visitors can register into the site on their own interest, it is not mandatory. This registration into the site permits the user to maintain and modify of the data submitted to the site. in fact StudySite.org requires no user registration. Users are free to visit StudySite.org, and navigate all its pages.

_Cookies and Web Beacons_

StudySite.org uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites, to help provide you with the best experience we can. 

How cookies help us:

  * Keep you loging in during login.
  * Improve our website for you
  * Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook
  * Offer you free services.
  * Increase the speed of the site

We do not use cookies to:

  * Collect any personally identifiable information 
  * Collect any sensitive information 
  * Pass personally identifiable data to third parties
  * Pay sales commissions

Rearn more about cookies we use below :

Cookies may be used on some pages within the website, such as logging into forums pages, or storing your preferences. Cookies and/or web beacons may also be used by third party websites who advertise on ObjectiveQuestions.in These are typically used to provide more personalized advertising to visitors as well as enabling the third party to track user trends.

You can choose to disable cookies using your web browser's settings. If you do choose to disable cookies, some functions of this website (and other websites) may not work as expected.

_Anti-Spam Policy_

StudySite.org is against in sending spam, unsolicited emails. You should not use our service and you are not authorized to use our referral or email services, for your personal or commercial purposes. By usage of this service you agreed that to our policies. Violating these policies in any manner subject to violation of respected laws and necessary action will be initiated against the defaulters. 

_Advertisements_

We fund our site by showing adverts as you browse our site. These adverts are usually managed by a partner specializing in providing adverts for multiple sites. Invariably these partners place cookies to collect anonymous data about the websites you visits so they can personalize the adverts to you, ensure that you don't see the same adverts too frequently and ultimately report to advertisers on which adverts are working.

_Links_

StudySite.org contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This privacy document applies only to StudySite.org.

If you find the content on StudySite.org useful, please consider linking to StudySite.org or mentioning ObjectiveQuestions.in on social media.

Thanks for visiting, and I hope you find StudySite.org useful!
